[
  {
    "question": "eins",
    "answer": "ένα",
    "phonetic": "**É**na"
  },
  {
    "question": "zwei",
    "answer": "δύο",
    "phonetic": "**DÍ**o"
  },
  {
    "question": "drei",
    "answer": "τρία",
    "phonetic": "**TRÍ**a"
  },
  {
    "question": "vier",
    "answer": "τέσσερα",
    "phonetic": "**TÉ**ssera"
  },
  {
    "question": "fünf",
    "answer": "πέντε",
    "phonetic": "**PÉN**de"
  },
  {
    "question": "sechs",
    "answer": "έξι",
    "phonetic": "**É**xi"
  },
  {
    "question": "sieben",
    "answer": "επτά",
    "phonetic": "ep**TÁ**"
  },
  {
    "question": "acht",
    "answer": "οκτώ",
    "phonetic": "ok**TÓ**"
  },
  {
    "question": "neun",
    "answer": "εννιά",
    "phonetic": "en**NIÁ**"
  },
  {
    "question": "zehn",
    "answer": "δέκα",
    "phonetic": "**DÉ**ka"
  },
  {
    "question": "elf",
    "answer": "έντεκα",
    "phonetic": "**ÉN**deka"
  },
  {
    "question": "zwölf",
    "answer": "δώδεκα",
    "phonetic": "**THÓ**deka"
  },
  {
    "question": "hundert",
    "answer": "εκατό",
    "phonetic": "eka**TÓ**"
  },
  {
    "question": "tausend",
    "answer": "χίλια",
    "phonetic": "**CHÍ**lia"
  },
  {
    "question": "aber",
    "answer": "αλλά",
    "phonetic": "al**LÁ**"
  },
  {
    "question": "weniger",
    "answer": "λιγότερο",
    "phonetic": "li**GÓ**tero"
  },
  {
    "question": "mehr",
    "answer": "περισσότερο",
    "phonetic": "peris**Ó**tero"
  },
  {
    "question": "früher",
    "answer": "πιο νωρίς",
    "phonetic": "pió no**RÍS**"
  },
  {
    "question": "später",
    "answer": "πιο αργά",
    "phonetic": "pió ar**GÁ**"
  },
  {
    "question": "wo",
    "answer": "πού",
    "phonetic": "**PÚ**"
  },
  {
    "question": "wann",
    "answer": "πότε",
    "phonetic": "**PÓ**te"
  },
  {
    "question": "wie",
    "answer": "πώς",
    "phonetic": "**PÓS**"
  },
  {
    "question": "wieviel",
    "answer": "πόσο",
    "phonetic": "**PÓ**so"
  },
  {
    "question": "dann",
    "answer": "τότε",
    "phonetic": "**TÓ**te"
  },
  {
    "question": "dort",
    "answer": "εκεί",
    "phonetic": "e**KÍ**"
  },
  {
    "question": "vielleicht",
    "answer": "ίσως",
    "phonetic": "**Í**sos"
  },
  {
    "question": "schlecht",
    "answer": "κακό",
    "phonetic": "ka**KÓ**"
  },
  {
    "question": "dies",
    "answer": "αυτό",
    "phonetic": "af**TÓ**"
  },
  {
    "question": "nicht",
    "answer": "όχι",
    "phonetic": "**Ó**chi"
  },
  {
    "question": "Problem",
    "answer": "πρόβλημα",
    "phonetic": "**PRÓ**vlima"
  },
  {
    "question": "helfen",
    "answer": "βοηθάω",
    "phonetic": "voï**THÁ**o"
  },
  {
    "question": "offen",
    "answer": "ανοιχτό",
    "phonetic": "ani**CHTÓ**"
  },
  {
    "question": "geschlossen",
    "answer": "κλειστό",
    "phonetic": "kli**STÓ**"
  },
  {
    "question": "kaputt",
    "answer": "χαλασμένο",
    "phonetic": "chala**SMÉ**no"
  },
  {
    "question": "kaufen",
    "answer": "αγοράζω",
    "phonetic": "agho**RÁ**zo"
  },
  {
    "question": "sprechen",
    "answer": "μιλάω",
    "phonetic": "mi**LÁ**o"
  },
  {
    "question": "bitte",
    "answer": "παρακαλώ",
    "phonetic": "paraka**LÓ**"
  }
]